# ARMAN GOLMAKAN

# Full Stack Software Developer

https://ArmanGolmakan.github.io

#### **Profile**

Motivated full stack software developer with 3 years of experience working across the fullstack of software development. Fast and eager leaner, supportive and reliable team player with a strong bias towards software quality and customer satisfaction.

## **Skills**

- Languages: Java, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, TypeScript, Python
- Frameworks: React, AngularJS, Angular, Redux, React Native, **Bootstrap**
- Technologies: Ajax, JSON, WebSockets, REST API, UNIX
- Methodologies: Agile Development, Git version control, UX/UI Responsive Design, Continuous Integration

#### **EDUCATION**

• Database: SQL

Bachelor of Science - Computer Science York University, Toronto 2021

# **CONTACT / SOCIAL**



arman.golmakan@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/arman1996



github.com/armangolmakan



647-000-0000

# HIGH QUALIFICATIONS

- Professional experience in developing and designing User Interface for web applications with deep insight using HTML 5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Angular 7, ReactJS, and NodeJS.
- Pleasant experience working in healthcare, accounting, auditing, and research domains.
- Maximizing applications' efficiency, data quality, scope, operability, and flexibility.
- Dedicated team Player with excellent, communication and Interpersonal skills.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## **FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER**

March 2022 - July 2024

# **BANK OF MONTRAL (BMO)**

- Developed and maintained web applications using React.js for the front end and Node.js/Express.js for the back end.
- Built responsive components and modules as per design guidelines.
- Collaborated with QA, designers, content strategists, digital managers and product owners to identify technical solutions and deliver high-quality software products.
- Identified and solved live prod issues. Accurately documented root cause and solution.

## SOFTWARE DEVELOPER, INTERN

Jan 2019 – Aug 2019

#### **CASEWARE INTERNATIONAL**

Caseware develops and sells software solutions for accounting, financial, risk and governance professionals.

- Developed auditing web applications using Angular framework and managed unexpected behavior of implemented functionality by writing tests.
- Architected and developed table filters, a functionality that allows auditors and accountants to quickly apply filters to menus and tables by showing/hiding different columns/rows.
- Communicated directly with squad members and product owners to accurately determine requirements.

## **WEB APP DEVELOPER**

May 2017 – August 2018

# **BIOSA-LABS**

BioSA is a research center focused on the development of biologically inspired sensor and actuator technologies.

- Researched computer vision and various detection and monitoring applications for AMD (Age Related Macular Degeneration)
- Developed web applications using HTML/CSS/JavaScript

## PROJECTS

#### PERSONAL PORTFOLIO WEBSITE:

Designed, architected, and developed a portfolio website using ReactJS and Bootstrap. https://ArmanGolmakan.github.io

## **MEDSCAN: Mobile App**

Designed and developed a React Native mobile application in a team of four. Medscan allows medical staff to easily scan a patient's fab using smartphones' built-in NFC technology. Patient's medical data is then stored in Google's firebase database.

HACKATHON LEAD ORGANIZER Organized and planned YorkUHacks 2018, York University's first major hackathon, where participants had to implement solutions for UN global issues. www.yorkuhacks.com

JAVA MARIO GAME Developed a 2D Mario Game with the use of Java and JavaFX. https://github.com/ArmanGolmakan/Mario Game